This is a list for the update of pvt tools released at 2014/08/01, when compared with the one released at 2014/07/31:

1. Add the following tools:

sn_read
mac_read
exitprogram
image_boot_change
fw_update_existing
fw_update_transfer

Notice that the tool 'image_boot_change' is used at the very end of the entire testing process. As far as I　know, the last step is aging_logcheck. So you can use the tool 'image_boot_change' after the 'aging_logcheck' tool.
Notice that the 2 fw_update tools(fw_update_existing and fw_update_transfer) are used for firmware update. Their difference usage is caused by whether the new firmware file exists at the device.


2. Modify the errorcode list

Modify the errorcode of sn_read， mac_read and aging_logcheck.

3. Modify the Readme files

Edit the Readme_ddr.txt
Add the Readme_image_boot_change.txt